I don't want to get it I don't want to get it No, no,
I don't want to get it
[Music]
Look who has come, yes, your new
friend
[Music] Yes, do you
cry or laugh with your friend,
what was his name, hello my new
friend is done
[Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] It is a
major operation, the
expense will be a lot
[Music]
You prepare for the operation, the
money is being arranged
[Music]
See, with just a tap of your fingers, you
can give someone a new life Just tap on the
donate option while buying an ICICI Lord health insurance policy for yourself or your loved ones
and help
We will also donate the matching amount of your donation So
let's join hands and extend a helping hand
ICICI Lord keeps its promises